const question = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Method of Array determines whether an array includes a certain value among its entries",
    answer: "includes",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Method of Array creates and returns a new string by concatenating all of the elements in this array, separate by commas or a specified separator string",
    answer: "join",
  },
  { id: 3, question: "Method of Array reverses an array", answer: "reverse" },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Method of Array creates a new array with all sub-array elements concatenated into it recursively up to the specified depth",
    answer: "flat",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Method of Array changes all elements within a range of indices in an array to a staic value",
    answer: "fill",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Method of Array returns a shallow copy of portion of an array into a new array object selected from start to end",
    answer: "slice",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Method of Array test whether at least one ellement in the array passes the test implemented by the provided function",
    answer: "some",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Method of Array changes the contents of an array by removing or replacing existing elements and/or adding new element in place",
    answer: "splice",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Method of instances adds the specified elements to the beginning of an array and returns the new length of the array",
    answer: "unshift",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Method of Array is used to merge two or more arrays",
    answer: "concat",
  },
];

export default question;